{
    "id": "7de7f69dfb4141099cd99f4a8558cf08",
    "title": "Adverbs worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "08ddc2253ecd4fd29df884f56e3e0ff9",
            "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ............................... go to bed at 10 o’clock.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "once",
                        "ever",
                        "usually"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have …………………. been to the USA.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "never",
                        "ever"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have been to Australia just …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "one",
                        "once",
                        "ones"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….. take a bath before I go to bed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "once",
                        "always",
                        "ever"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My grandparents live in Kerala. I visit them .......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "once",
                        "often"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My friends are ............................................. non-smokers.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "most",
                        "mostly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was ....................................... impressed with her performance.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "such",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ....................................... go for a walk in the park.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "some time",
                        "sometime",
                        "sometimes"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I watch English films ....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "once",
                        "always",
                        "occasionally"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They ...................................... go out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rare",
                        "once",
                        "rarely"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}